





Last Active: 22-Jan-21

Verified : Number | Email - id

21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Management, Use Case Modeling, UML, Scrum, SDLC, Waterfall, MySQL, Tableau

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills | Projects |

Key Skills: Business Analyst, Business Analysis, Requirement Gathering, Software Engineering, Program Management, System Analysis, New Product Development, Gap Analysis, FRS, Impact Analysis, Change

## Summary

Well known about requirement gathering, requirement analysis, monitoring development, documentation, testing, maintenance and support.

Excellent technical writing skills to create Business Requirements Document (BRD),

Functional Specifications Document (FSD), Nonfunctional Requirements Document, User Manual and Use Cases Specifications.

Excellent business, communication, and presentation skills.

Comprehensive knowledge of and Solid experience of Agile and SCRUMmethodologies.

Well versed in Requirements/Change Management, Impact Analysis and Gap Analysis.

Interviewed SMEs and Stakeholders to get a better understanding of client business processes and gather business requirements.

Experience in developing Scope/Msion Documentation, Project Plan, tracking Project Process, and managing resources to ensure successful delivery.

## **Work Experience**

Girnar Software Pvt. Ltd.(CarDekho) as IT Business Analyst Jan 2020 to Till Date

Analyzing customer requirements and requirement gathering.

Client Interaction

Formulating Scope of Work.

Translate stakeholder requirements into different tangible deliverables such as FRS, BRD,

Workflow and process flow diagrams, data flow diagrams.

Prototyping and Wireframing.

Identify scope of Business Automation.

Testing and validation of product.

Analyzing web performance with the help of Google Analytics and optimization of the same for further enhancements.

Preparation of user stories and test case documents.

Helical Auto Technology India Private Limited as Development Engineer Jul 2018 to Dec 2019

Analyzing customer requirements and requirement gathering. Development of inventory management module in ERP system. Formulating Scope of work.

New product development.

Production Part Approval Process (PPAP) documentation. Identify scope of Business Administration.

Testing and validation of product.

# **Important**

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

^ Back to Top

#### **Education**

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Mechanical) from Pune University in 2018

PG: NA (na) from na in 0

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs: Diploma (Mechanical) Professional Scrum Master I Agile Business Analyst Advanced Certified Business Analyst Scrum Foundation Professional Certificate Scrum Fundamentals Certified

^ Back to Top

#### IT Skills

Version	Last Used	Experience
	2020	2 Year(s) 6 Month(s)
3.lnk	2020	2 Year(s) 6 Month(s)

^ Back to Top

## Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Marathi				

^ Back to Top

# **Projects**

Project Title: RTO- Vehicle Information Application

Client: GirnarSoft

Nature of Employment: Full Time

Project Location: Jaipur

Role: Other

Skill Used: - Requirement gathering and elicitation

- Product management
- Wireframing and prototyping
- Stakeholder management
- Technical solutions
- Market analysis
- Documentation

Role Description: Business Analyat Project Details: About the App:

Check RC Status with vehicle number & check all Driving Licence details online

Amust-have app for your vehicle-related information. It comes handy when you need details regarding your driving license, vehicle challan, service history and Registration information.

Duration: Jan 2020 - Jan 2021 Onsite / Offsite: Onsite

Team Size: 5

Customer Profile Management:

User can get all personal and vehicle-related information at a click. Update all your personal details along with digital copies of your identity proofs like RC, DL, Aadhar Card, Pan card, etc.

RTO registration number, driving license details or your vehicle registration details, pull out all vehicle owner information with just a click.

#### Vehicle Information

Just enter the vehicle registration number and find all details of vehicle-related information on the screen. Through this app, you can source the following RTO vehicle information:

Owner name Registration Date

Registration Date
Registration Authority

Fnaine Number

Chassis Number Vehicle Model Vehicle Fuel type Vehicle State and City

and more

^ Back to Top

#### **Affirmative Action**

Physically Challenged: No

#### **Work Authorization**

Category: General

Job Type: Permanent
Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQs - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.